Guide to the Lively Arts at Stanford Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Theatre Sans Fil - Sept. 29, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Trio di Milano - Oct. 28, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Ughi, Uto (cancelled) - Dec. 5, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Vogel, Harold - June 15, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Zuckerman/Karr/Lewis - Oct. 12, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 10)